I want to shout out every woman who is undoing the wiring of being the cool girl.
The cool girl is the girl who through many years of being embroiled in situationships
or just literally even being just dealt with by dudes in a manner of confrontation all the time,
takes on the essence of I'm the cool girl, easy breezy, and we always do it to our detriment.
We think we're doing it to be presenting as easygoing, to be presenting as like non-obstructive.
However, we always internally feel like we are not being served.
We always internally feel like we are lying to ourselves, right?
And then we also then internally have to deal with it because the cool girl is not going to bring that to the person.
I feel like so often the cool girl does not set their expectation and then they are upset later
because the expectation wasn't met, even though what they actually presented was a false expectation.
The expectation they presented was everything is easy breezy, you know, and so it's whatever.
When the reality is like, no, it's not easy fucking breezy.
So basically, shout out to my cool girls who have grown out of this and who have become aware that we need to be clear in what we want.
Also, in order to allow the person to demonstrate if they are able to provide what we want and what we expect.
That's important.
You know, and some of these things, they would never have been noticed earlier in my life
because I just didn't have the healing and the self-love to even be able to, like, acknowledge them.
So many of us have been awakened to that.
So many of us have been awakened to our own self-awareness,
which is what allowed us to not only notice the narcissism in our relationships,
the harmfulness, the abuse in our relationships,
but also the narcissism, the harmfulness, and the abuse in our governments, right?
And in this world.
Cut out the corporate middlemen and purchase my music directly from me.
Head to amandadiva.bandcamp.com
and pay whatever price you want for Truth Translator.
This ain't a movement.
It's movement music.
Thank you.